Human beings have always loved reviews: word of mouth has long been regarded as one of the most valuable marketing tools available to a company.
人类一向喜欢看评价：长期以来，口碑一直被视为公司所能利用的最有价值的营销工具之一。
Consumers enjoy reading and giving reviews.
消费者喜欢阅读评价，也喜欢写评价。
However, the problem is that a lot of the reviews are fake.
然而，问题是很多评价是假的。
Shabnam Azimi and Alexander Krasnikov of Loyola University of Chicago and Kwong Chan of Northeastern University recently published a study on fake reviews.
芝加哥洛约拉大学的沙布纳姆·阿齐米、亚历山大·克拉斯尼科夫和美国东北大学的Kwong Chan最近发表了一项关于虚假评论的研究。
The study used a data set of 1,600 reviews of Chicago hotels.
这项研究使用了一个包含1600条芝加哥酒店评论的数据集。
Some of them were real; others were fake.
其中一些是真的，另一些是假的。
The reviews were presented to 400 subjects.
这些评论被呈现给400名受试者。
Each subject got eight reviews to read: a balanced set of two positive fake, two positive real, two negative fake and two negative real, presented in a random order.
每位受试者阅读八条评论：两条虚假正面评论、两条真实正面评论、两条虚假负面评论和两条真实负面评论，搭配均衡，按随机顺序呈现。
The reviews were written by real people who were given information about the hotel.
这些评论由真人撰写，他们事先拿到了所评酒店的相关信息。
The results show that consumers generally trust negative reviews more than positive ones.
结果显示，与正面评论相比，消费者普遍更相信负面评论。
Moreover, we humans tend to assume that positive reviews might be fake.
此外，我们人类往往会认为正面评论可能是假的。
“Overall, negative reviews are less common.
“总的来说，负面评论比较少见。
So, we pay more attention to them.
所以我们会更关注它们。
When a negative review is fake, we get tricked,” Azimi says.
当一条负面评论是假的时，我们就上当了，”阿齐米说。
When it came to faking a review, length was important to believability, as was detail.
说到伪造评论，篇幅对可信度很重要，细节也是如此。
A long, negative review of a hotel, complete with lots of information, tended to convince participants.
一条篇幅长、信息详尽的负面酒店评论，往往能让参与者信服。
A lengthy, positive review, on the other hand, was regarded as suspicious, and participants tended to trust writers that kept their glowing reviews short.
另一方面，一条长篇的正面评论会被视为可疑，参与者往往信任那些把热情洋溢的好评写得简短的作者。
Emotion was also important in convincing readers — or the lack of emotion, at least.
情感在说服读者方面也很重要——或者至少是缺乏情感这一点很重要。
Azimi says study participants tended not to trust reviews where the writers expressed their feelings in a big way.
阿齐米说，研究参与者往往不相信那些作者强烈表达自己情感的评论。
The more dispassionate that negative write-up, the more likely it was to take the reader in.
负面评论写得越冷静客观，就越有可能骗过读者。
The fake reviews written for Azimi’s study were put together by humans, but increasingly, fake reviews are being written by AI, which makes them look more real.
为阿齐米的研究撰写的假评论是由人编写的，但如今越来越多的假评论由人工智能撰写，这让它们看起来更真实。
Though many companies use algorithms to weed out fake reviews, Azimi points out that the machines are programmed by humans, and given our limited ability to spot fake reviews, this isn’t a good sign.
尽管许多公司使用算法来剔除虚假评论，但阿齐米指出，机器是由人编程的，而考虑到我们识别假评论的能力有限，这可不是个好兆头。